allaboutjazz.com 2013-12-17

# All About Jazz Privacy Policy

**Your credit card transaction at All About Jazz is 100% safe - We Guarantee It.**

We have been successfully processing secure credit card transactions since 1997.

When we request personal information from you (such as name, address, phone number and credit card number) it is done on our secure servers. We use industry standard technology to protect confidential information - SSL (Secured Socket Layer) - an advanced encryption technology that makes personal information unreadable as it travels over the Internet. In addition, once your transaction is complete, your credit card number is deleted from our database.

We are so confident in our security, that we guarantee you'll pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your credit card as a result of shopping at All About Jazz.

Federal law limits your liability for unauthorized charges to your account. The Fair Credit Billing Act states that your credit card company (creditor) cannot hold you liable for more than $50 in the unlikely event a fraudulent charge occurs on your account. If you encounter a fraudulent credit card charge at All About Jazz, don't worry, we'll pay the first $50. No credit card risk - Guaranteed. 

**Guarantee Details**

In the unlikely event of a fraudulent use of your credit card at All About Jazz, you must notify your credit card company in accordance with their rules and procedures.

If your creditor holds you responsible for any of the $50, let us know. All About Jazz will cover the full liability for you up to $50.

Please note that All About Jazz will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at All About Jazz while using our secure servers.

We realize that customers are concerned about how the information they provide online will be used. We are committed to protecting your privacy and will use the information we collect about you to process your order and provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details regarding our Privacy Policy.

**Privacy Information**

**What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use It?**

When you place an order, we ask you to provide information to complete your order by filling out and submitting an online form. This information may include your name, telephone numbers, mailing address, e-mail address and credit card information. All information regarding our online customers is stored on a highly secured server that is not accessible through the Internet.

When you participate in an online contest or survey, we may ask you for personal information such as name or e-mail address to complete this process. Your participation in these events is voluntary and information collected will be used to enhance your future shopping/visiting experiences at All About Jazz and provide you with special offers that we believe will benefit you. To continuously assess the value of our online shopping/visiting experience, we may track the way customers use our site; however, this information is analyzed only in the aggregate and not at the individual level. All About Jazz and Vision X Software (AAJ's parent company) has a strong history of providing excellent customer service and our goal is to continue this tradition.

All About Jazz is committed to the preservation of online privacy for all of its Web site visitors. We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes other than to enrich your experience at AAJ.

Any e-mail we send you will also include information on how to unsubscribe.

**Cookies and How We Use Them**

A cookie is a small file stored on your computer by a Web site to give you a unique ID. Cookies help make it easier for you to use our site, and they help us provide you with the information you need--when and where you need it. Cookies provided by our Web site do not contain any credit card or personal information. We do not know who you are unless you provided that information voluntarily. All About Jazz uses cookies to track new visitors to our site and recognize past customers so that we may present more personalized content. We do not use cookies to personally identify anonymous site visitors. 

All About Jazz uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. All About Jazz is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Contacting All About Jazz**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with these Web sites, you can contact: [privacy@visionx.com](mailto:privacy@visionx.com).
